Curto, Ernest; Papers apap238
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1946-1965; Undated; 1; 9.2 cubic ft.
  - Niagara Project- State Joint Legislative Committee to Study Assessment and Taxation, 1956; 1959 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Premium Discount Company Grant, 1960; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Premium Finance- Against, 1960 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Premium Finance- For (folders 1 and 2 of 3), 1960; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28-29)
  - Premium Finance- For (folder 3 of 3), 1960; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Premium Finance- General Debate, 1960; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Public Authorities Regulation, 1960 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Public Authorities Regulation, 1961 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Public Authorities Regulation, 1962 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Public Service Commission- Re Lehigh Valley Matter, 1962; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Railroads, Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Railroad Elimination, 1946-1951; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Reapportionment- Correspondence, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Reapportionment- Legislation, Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Reapportionment- Legislation- Compliance Act Bill, Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11-12)
  - Reapportionment- Maps, 1960 (Oversized 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Reapportionment- Maps (Highway), 1960; 1964 (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
  - Reapportionment- Press Coverage and Releases, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13-14)
  - Reapportionment- Reports and Data, 1960; 1962; 1964; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Reapportionment- Reports and Data, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Reapportionment- Reports and Data, 1964; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Registration Fee Increase, 1963; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19-21)
  - Regional Information Center, 1965 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Republican Party, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Resolutions (Completed), 1960; 1963-1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Resolutions (Pending), 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Resolution- Sabbath, 1953; 1959-1960; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Rules Requests, 1960 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Scholarship Letters, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - School Boards, 1963-1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - School Districts (Completed), 1960 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Speeches, Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - State Aid to School Districts, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Strikebreakers- Correspondence Re Laverne Proposal, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Strikebreakers- Correspondence Re Laverne Proposal, 1963 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Strikebreakers- Legislative Materials, 1961-1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Strikebreakers- Notes, 1959; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Strikebreakers- Opposing Memos, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Strikebreakers- Other State Laws and Local Ordinances, 1960-1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Strikebreakers- Press Coverage, 1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Strikebreakers- Public Hearing, 1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Strikebreakers- Special Committee of Investigation, 1959; 1963 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Strikebreakers- Speech, Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Strikebreakers- Support Memos, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - State University, 1963 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Teachers' Pensions, 1960; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Time Off To Vote, 1960 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Tuitions-State College, 1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal, 1959-1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15-17)
  - Urban Renewal- City of Niagara Falls, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal- Department of Commerce Publications, 1963-1965 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal- Division of Housing Publications, 1963 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal- Division of Housing Publications, 1959-1960; 1962-1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Urban Renewal- Division of Housing Publications, 1962-1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Urban Renewal- Housing and Urban Development Committee- Community Service Society, 1961 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Urban Renewal- Housing and Urban Development Committee- Community Service Society, 1962 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Urban Renewal- Housing and Urban Development Committee- Community Service Society, 1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Urban Renewal- Joint Legislative Committee on Housing and Urban Renewal, 1961; 1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Urban Renewal- Legislation, 1961 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Urban Renewal- Legislative Research Service Publications, 1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Urban Renewal- Memos, 1961; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Urban Renewal- Metropolitan Areas Study, 1959 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Urban Renewal- Metropolitan Areas Study, 1960 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32-33)
  - Urban Renewal- Niagara Falls Community Problems Conference, 1961 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal- Notes, 1960-1961; Undated (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal- Planning Chart, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal- Press Coverage, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal- Public Housing Reports, 1963 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal- Public Housing Reports, 1964 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal- Sewers, 1962-1963 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal- Talking Points, 1962 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Weekly Letters, 1960; Undated (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
- Bills, 1956-1964; Undated; 2; 2.6 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically, and by bill number.
  This series, divided into two subseries, contains legislation that for the most part was introduced by Assemblyman Ernest Curto, and supporting materials, including memos, correspondence regarding the bills, and newspaper clippings.
  The first subseries contains bound copies of the bills that Curto introduced. Each book contains bills from one session, and on the inside of the cover is a list of the bills contained in the book. Curto made notations on some of the covers, as well as on some of the bills, as to the fate of the legislation. Also in this subseries, researchers will find book covers that would have originally contained his personal bills, but arrived at the archives without their contents intact.
  The second subseries contains the files that Curto kept about each bill that he introduced in the New York State Assembly. He kept an individual file on each bill, and in some cases, more than one file if that bill had been amended significantly. The bill files contain copies of the legislation and, in some cases, notes, correspondence, newspaper clippings or memos related to the bill. The archivist elected to retain the original folder names used by Curto and his staff, and made copies of the original folders whenever Curto had made notations on them.
  Researchers should note that there are several bills in this subseries that were not introduced by Curto. There are several bills that Curto kept that relate to a special session of the legislature that was called by Governor Nelson Rockefeller in the autumn of 1964, and the archivist elected to include them in this subseries.
  Researchers should be aware that the bills in this series relate to the latter half of Curto’s term in office. Earlier bills, those from 1948-1953, were in folders with correspondence. Since many of these bills are stamped “Compliments of Ernest Curto,” and not attached to other materials, the archivist elected to keep them in the correspondence series.
  - Bound Bill Books, 1956-1963; Undated; 2.1
    - Bound Bill Book, 1956 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
    - Bound Bill Book, 1957 (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
    - Bill Book Front Cover, 1958 (Oversized 2, Folder 3)
    - Bound Bill Book, 1959 (Oversized 2, Folder 4)
    - Bound Bill Book, 1960 (Oversized 2, Folder 5)
    - Bill Book Back Cover, 1961 (Oversized 2, Folder 6)
    - Bound Bill Book, 1961 (Oversized 2, Folder 7)
    - Bound Bill Book, 1963 (Oversized 2, Folder 8)
    - Bill Book Front Cover, Undated (Oversized 2, Folder 9)
    - Bill Book Front Cover, Undated (Oversized 2, Folder 10)
    - Bill Book Back Cover, Undated (Oversized 2, Folder 11)
  - Bill Files, 1958-1964; Undated; 2.2
    - INT. 4268- Tax, Lessees of Tax Exempt Property, 1958-1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 1)
    - Resolution 98- Alcohol Wholesalers, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 2)
    - INT. 687- Public Service, Inspection of Gas Appliances, 1958-1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 3)
    - INT. 932- Retirement, Social Security, and Education, Final Average and Salary, 1958-1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 4)
    - INT. 1105- Repeal of the Youth Court Act, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 5)
    - INT. 1106- Repeal of the Youth Court Act, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 6)
    - INT. 1174- Niagara Falls Arterial Highways, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 7)
    - INT. 1175- Niagara Falls Hospitals, Water Supply, 1958-1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 8)
    - INT. 1176- Public Works, Mineral Aggregates, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 9)
    - INT. 1745- Real Property, Lessees of Tax Exempt Property, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 10)
    - INT. 1960- State Prison Guard Retirement, Age 50, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 11)
    - INT. 1961- Education, Ophthalmic Dispensing, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 12)
    - INT. 1962- Education, Duly Licensed Optometrists, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 13)
    - INT. 2001- Labor, Unemployment Insurance, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 14)
    - INT. 2002- Penal, Admission of Children to Bowling Alleys, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 15)
    - INT. 2118- Retirement and Social Security, Optional Retirement at 55, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 16)
    - INT. 2377- Education, Teachers' Pensions, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 17)
    - INT. 2378- Civil Service, Suspension of Pensions, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 18)
    - INT. 2379- Highway, Thruway Approach, Exit Lights, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 19)
    - INT. 2380- Code of Criminal Procedure- Niagara Falls Director of Public Safety Designation as a Peace Officer, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 20)
    - INT. 2443- Optometric Care at Local 32-B Health Center, 1958-1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 21)
    - INT. 2461- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Health Center, Inc., 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 22)
    - INT. 2525- Public Officers, Leaves of Absence for Firemen, Conventions, 1955; 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 23)
    - INT. 2526- Retirement and Social Security- Reports to Director of Social Security, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 24)
    - INT. 2710- Education, Jurisdiction of Attendance Officers, Children on Indian Reservations, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 25)
    - INT. 2711- Education, Apportionment of Aid to Enlarged Districts, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 26)
    - INT. 2797- State Finance, Court of Claims Judgments, Payments, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 27)
    - INT. 2886- Niagara Falls Arterial Highways, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 28)
    - INT. 2887- Education, Prior Service Credit for Teachers, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 29)
    - INT. 3238- Workmen's Compensation, Computation of Disability Benefits, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 30)
    - INT. 3283- Civil Service, Suspension of Pensions, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 31)
    - INT. 3317- Civil Service, Suspension of Pensions, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 32)
    - INT. 3402- Education, Boards in Union-Free School Districts, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 33)
    - INT. 3468- Education, Teachers' Pensions, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 34)
    - INT. 3671- Judiciary, Drawing of Jurors, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 35)
    - INT. 3672- Criminal Procedure Code, Application for Remission of Forfeiture, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 36)
    - INT. 3673- Criminal Procedure Code, Bail Bond Premiums, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 37)
    - INT. 3674- Civil Practice, Privilege Between Patients and Doctors, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 38)
    - INT. 4030- Public Authorities, Power Authority, Payments in Lieu of Taxes, 1957; 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 39)
    - INT. 4031- Public Authorities, Power Authority, Payments in Lieu of Taxes, 1957; 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 40)
    - INT. 4032- Public Authorities, Power Authority, Payments in Lieu of Taxes, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 41)
    - INT. 4141- Public Service, Removal of Exemption Zones for Movers of Household Goods, 1959; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 42)
    - INT. 4194- Payments to Schools in Lieu of Taxes, Power Authority, 1959 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 43)
    - INT. 122- Highway, Thruway Approach, Exit Lights, 1959-1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 44)
    - INT. 123- Alcoholic Beverage Control, Minimum Resale Prices for Beer, 1959-1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 45)
    - INT. 148- Education, Retired Teachers, Additional Pensions, 1959-1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 46)
    - INT. 149- Retirement, Social Security, and Education, Final Average Salary, 1957; 1959-1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 47)
    - INT. 890- State Prison Guards Retirement, Age 50, 1959-1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 48)
    - INT. 934- Real Property, Notices of Vacation, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 49)
    - INT. 1013- Youth Court Act, Repeal, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 50)
    - INT. 1014- Education, School District Board President, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 51)
    - INT. 1015- Education, Proceedings Against Districts, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 52)
    - INT. 1016- Education, Claims Against Districts, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 53)
    - INT. 1017- Criminal Code, Youth Court Provision, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 54)
    - INT. 1018- Public Works, Quarry Licenses, 1959-1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 55)
    - INT. 1322- Personal Property, Retail Installment Contracts, 1959-1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 56)
    - INT. 1323- Personal Property, Conditional Sales Contracts, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 57)
    - INT. 1370- Housing, Service of Process, 1959-1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 58)
    - INT. 1446- State Power Authority, School District Appropriations, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 59)
    - INT. 1551- Banking and Insurance, Premium Finance, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 60)
    - INT. 1641- Workmen's Compensation, Non-occupational Disability Benefits Increase, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 61)
    - INT. 1642- Labor, Unemployment Insurance Benefit Year, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 62)
    - INT. 1861- Penal, Bowling Alleys, Children, 1959-1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 63)
    - INT. 1862- Real Property, Abandonment by Tenant, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 64)
    - INT. 1863- Education, Contact Lenses Regulation, 1960-1961; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 65)
    - INT. 2077- Multiple Residence, Nuisances, Definition, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 66)
    - INT. 2109- Multiple Residence, Institutions, Exit Regulations, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 67)
    - INT. 2110- Low-cost Housing Project Loans, 1959-1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 68)
    - INT. 2191- Multiple Residence, Transom Specifications, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 69)
    - INT. 2192- Education, Teachers' Disability Retirement, 1959-1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 70)
    - INT. 2193- Co-op Housing Company, Tenants, Regulations, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 71)
    - INT. 2563- To Amend the Public in Relation to Plan Required for Realty Subdivisions, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 72)
    - INT. 2704- Education, Unfair Education Practices, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 73)
    - INT. 2985- Education, Witnesses at Hearings, 1959-1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 74)
    - INT. 2986- Education, School Fire Drills, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 75)
    - INT. 2987- Town, Niagara County, School Taxes, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 76)
    - INT. 3077- Multiple Dwelling, New York City. Night Watchmen, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 77)
    - INT. 3078- Lien, Mortgages, Lien Security, 1959-1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 78)
    - INT. 3079- Niagara County State Highway Designs, Pine Avenue, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 79)
    - INT. 3080- Niagara County State Highway Designs, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 80)
    - INT. 3173- Niagara Falls Arterial Highways, Military, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 81)
    - INT. 3174- Housing, Tenant Relocations, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 82)
    - INT. 3175- Limited Profit Housing, State Loans, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 83)
    - INT. 3241- Education, Optometrists Advertising, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 84)
    - INT. 3242- Non-occupational Disability Benefits, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 85)
    - INT. 3243- Redevelopment Companies, Earnings Use, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 86)
    - INT. 3325- Election, Designating Petitions, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 87)
    - INT. 3410- Banking, Premium Finance Agencies, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 88)
    - INT. 3411- Redevelopment Companies, Realty Transfers, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 89)
    - INT. 3469- Niagara Falls City Court, Summons, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 90)
    - INT. 3529- Agriculture and Markets, Retail Food Sales, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 91)
    - INT. 3605- Printing, Print Contract Awards, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 92)
    - INT. 3606- Multiple Dwelling, New York City Night Watchmen, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 93)
    - INT. 3723- Education, License Suspensions, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 94)
    - INT. 3724- Limited Profit Housing Corporation, Notes, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 95)
    - INT. 4000- Mineral Aggregates, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 96)
    - INT. 4020- Real Property, Relation to Licensing Nonresidents, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 97)
    - INT. 4111- Penal, Strikebreakers, Recruiters, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 98)
    - INT. 4234- State Power Authority Local Payments, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 99)
    - INT. 4323- Real Property, Qualifications for Estate Broker Licenses, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 100)
    - INT. 4324- Real Property, Qualifications for Estate Broker Licenses, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 101)
    - INT. 4352- Municipal, Urban Renewal Agencies, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 102)
    - INT. 4359- Housing, Municipal Housing Agency, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 103)
    - INT. 4360- Multiple Dwelling, Fire Protection, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 104)
    - INT. 4366- Housing, Destruction of Records, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 105)
    - INT. 4502- Annexation, Wheatfield, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 106)
    - INT. 4503- Annexation, Town of Niagara, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 107)
    - INT. 4601- Rules Committee, Minimum Wage Bill, 1960; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 108)
    - INT. 4613- Rules Committee, Kerosene Heaters, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 109)
    - INT. 205- Retirement, Social Security, and Education, Final Average Salary, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 110)
    - INT. 236- Niagara Falls, Serial Bonds for Water Improvement, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 111)
    - INT. 255- Civil Practice, Compensation of a Committee, 1961; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 112)
    - INT. 256- Repeal of the Youth Court Act, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 113)
    - INT. 258- Education and Executive, Discrimination by Educational Institutions, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 114)
    - INT. 259- Lien, Mortgages Against Real and Personal Property, 1961; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 115)
    - INT. 320- Vehicle and Traffic. Limited Operators and Chauffeurs Licenses, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 116)
    - INT. 349- General Business- Strikebreakers, 1960-1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 117)
    - INT. 917- Banking, Premium Finance, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 118)
    - INT. 918- Lien, Chattel Mortgages by Dealers, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 119)
    - INT. 919- Personal Property and Lien, Filing and Refiling of Conditional Sales Contracts, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 120)
    - INT. 920- Personal Property, Retail Installment Credit Agreements, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 121)
    - INT. 921- Personal Property, Promissory Notes for Real Property Improvements, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 122)
    - INT. 922- Personal Property, Retail Installment Contracts, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 123)
    - INT. 923- Personal Property, Retail Installment Contracts, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 124)
    - INT. 1151- Public Housing, Limited-Profit Housing Companies, 1960-1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 125)
    - INT. 1152- Public Housing and Executive, Commissioner and Division of Housing, 1960-1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 126)
    - INT. 1153- Public Housing, Power of Commission of Housing Over Projects, 1960-1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 127)
    - INT. 1373- Labor, Maximum Hours for Firemen, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 128)
    - INT. 1374- Labor, Maximum Hours for Firemen, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 129)
    - INT. 1375- State Prison Guard Retirement, Age 50, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 130)
    - INT. 1376- Retirement, Social Security, and Education, Final Average Salary, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 131)
    - INT. 1377- Education, Teachers' Pensions, 1961; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 132)
    - INT. 1378- Executive, State Building Code Council, 1960-1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 133)
    - INT. 1553- Surrogate's Court Act, Administrator for Missing Person's Dependents, 1961; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 134)
    - INT. 1554- Surrogate's Court Act, Protection of Property of Missing Persons, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 135)
    - INT. 1602- Multiple Dwelling, Night Watchmen, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 136)
    - INT. 1603- Labor, Unemployment Insurance, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 137)
    - INT. 1604- Workmen's Compensation, Hospitalization Benefits, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 138)
    - INT. 1605- Workmen's Compensation, Disability Benefits Commutation, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 139)
    - INT. 1606- State Printing, Qualifications of Bidders, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 140)
    - INT. 1720- Judiciary, Appointment of Stenographers, 1961; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 141)
    - INT. 1866- Education, Osteopathy, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 142)
    - INT. 2015- Personal Property, Protection for Buyers of Merchandise Certifications, 1961; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 143)
    - INT. 2100- Education, Death Benefits for Teachers, 1961; Undated (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 144)
    - INT. 2459- Agriculture and Markets, Proper Marking of Food Weights, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 145)
    - INT. 2665- Court of Claims, Jurisdiction of Carter Compensation Claim, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 146)